I'm looking for a crime boss
from Korea.
Well, I wanted to meet you,
but this will do.
She's hiding here
in the Philippines.
She changed her name,
even her face.
Joey, she's not answering
my calls.
Maybe the kid's just busy.
I'm also nervous.
Who are you really,
and why do you keep showing up?
How did you meet him?
He's my stalker!
I saved your life twice.
So my name is Lee Jin Ho.
I'm from the National
Intelligence Service in Korea.
Why are you following me?
The woman in the video,
the one you posted on the
internet.
That's what I'm looking for.
My problem now is Jin Ho!
He recognized me! He saw me!
You're not going anywhere.
Let's listen to him first.
What if this is connected
to your father's case?
Give me your cell phones.
Your gun.
I really don't trust
that Andrew.
I don't think he sleeps
at someone's house, right?
I knew it, you're really lying
about trusting Jin Ho.
Step away from my things.
Keep her out of this.
This is between you and me.
Can you stop?
Joey?
Joey!
If you want to kill each other,
don't involve other people,
okay?
Jin Ho, what are you doing?
Why are you doing this?
Joey, are you okay?
What's this? Hey!
He started first.
Why were you looking
at my stuff?
To make sure you are legit.
We can't just trust you.
Then you could've asked!
You didn't have to go
through my bag.
Again, I don't trust you.
I need proof for myself.
If there's anyone who shouldn't
be trusted here,
it's you because you
just used us.
What?
Yes, I know that's why you
want us to stay,
because you want to put this
story on your vlog.
You don't care if we get in
danger
as long as you have a story
to tell, right?
You're already caught, Boy.
That's where you're good at.
What? You can't say anything,
can you?
Because it's true.
You're good at getting other
people into trouble.
Isn't that what you did
to my father?
And now, what are you going
to do to us?
Can someone tell me
what's going on right now?
It's like this.
She...
He...
Joey hates Andrew.
You don't have to explain
to them.
Jin Ho, thank you for saving
my life twice,
but you don't have to worry
about me anymore.
Let's go.
Nothing yet?
Nothing.
I've been trying to book
for a while now.
But just be steady.
Someone will accept it too.
It's a good thing the Korean
gave us our cellphone back.
He should be.
Don't he dare not to or else
he'll really get it from me.
Aren't you tired yet?
You see, it's already morning.
Can you please stop including
this in the days
you're going to ruin?
Okay, okay. I might be wrong,
but there's a reason.
I don't need your explanation.
You know what I need?
I need you to stay away
from me
because I don't want
to see you again!
Driver!
Let's go, Joey.
Boss Budol, what now?
Let's go on our own ways.
Driver...
This is not over yet, Joey.
What, let's go?
We're just being suspicious.
No one's following us, right?
It's quiet.
No one's around.
So that means those who followed
us don't know where we live.
Yes.
Thank God, we're safe.
For now.
What the hell?
Hey, compose yourself.
Sorry.
Sir!
Yes?
Good morning.
Andrew Dizon, by the way.
What?
Are you looking for trouble
with us in uniform again?
Sir, I'm just reporting
the truth.
Like now, I'm just here
to find out the truth.
Okay, okay.
Maybe you'll say something else,
so I'll tell you.
This is a gang war,
it's not the first time
this has happened in this area.
Or maybe you'll blame it
on the police again.
No, Sir.
Thank you, Sir.
Is that it?
Aren't we going to investigate?
Well, let's go.
You lost control
of the situation, Lisa.
You even hurt yourself.
I had to spend money cleaning up
the mess you made last night.
It wasn't supposed to be
like that.
You know me.
I work clean.
But last night, there was an
unexpected complication.
And that complication?
Will that be a problem
for us again?
I'll take care of Jin Ho.
Don't worry.
Make sure of it.
We already tied up one loose end
with Major Delgado.
Don't start another problem.
It's good that Parak fixed
the mess you made.
We just made it look like
a gang war happened,
so there weren't too many
questions.
There's no need to complicate
things.
You're welcome.
Did you ask your people
if they saw the flash drive?
No...
No, why? What's in it?
It contains a video
of me and Ramon
that I need to recover.
What does that mean?
Can the flash drive
still be fixed?
Negative.
Is it really impossible
to do something?
Why don't you try again?
Aren't I really impressed
with you
because you're so good at that?
You're really fooling me,
but okay.
I'll find a way to do this.
I really need something else
to fix this.
Okay, Peter, okay,
let's find a way because that's
the only thing
that can really help Father.
Don't worry. We'll find a way.
I know how important this is
for you.
That's why so many other people
want it.
Think about it. We almost died
because of this.
Joey already has the flash
drive,
but...
But what?
But there's someone else
after it.
Joey almost got herself killed.
And even though we asked
for help,
the flash drive is still
not working.
But you know your daughter,
she'll find a way to fix
the flash drive.
I told her not to interfere.
Well, she inherited that
from someone else.
But...
we have a bigger problem.
I think the people we
encountered last night
have connections to the police.
You know, that's what I
suspected too.
Ramon records all their
meetings,
and there's a name that always
comes up Codename, Parak.
Parak could be anyone.
I think that Parak
has a position,
whoever he is.
Do you have any other info
that might help us?
You know, I'm still studying
the codes.
The others, maybe timestamps,
but I'm still not sure.
I'll study them.
I'll let you know.
Andrew, I have a favor
to ask of you.
If you can, tell Joey not
to interfere.
First of all,
I'm here to help you.
Second, she doesn't trust me.
She won't listen to me.
Third, I'm not here to babysit
your daughter.
Is that software really 4k?
You know,
this is the cheapest one.
Because recovery tools
are really more expensive.
Worse, we're not sure
if it can be done.
This laptop is already old.
Do you need a new laptop?
It doesn't have to be brand new.
All you need is high specs.
We've already had a hard time
getting you back,
and now you'll make us
spend more money.
Lord, help, please.
Hello, Mother?
Joey...
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
I miss you so much.
You know, it's so quiet here
at home.
What do you think, Joey?
I'm thinking about finding
a job first.
Are you crying, Joey?
What happened?
I'm just frustrated.
Frustrated? Why?
I'm doing everything
I can to help Father.
I just want him to be free
so we can be whole again.
Joey...
I understand what you're
feeling,
what you're going through.
But what you want to happen
is impossible.
So I hope you don't blame
yourself.
Well, that's the thing.
I've found evidence to help
Father but it's broken.
It's not easy to fix.
Joey, don't solve the problem
alone.
You know, it's better
to call your Godfather Diego.
Yeah, that's it!
Yes?
You know, your mother was right.
I think that's what you should
have done first.
Why not?
Didn't Father say not to tell
anyone?
Maybe someone else would get
hurt.
Friendship! Boarders! Get out,
quickly! What's with you?
Hurry, I'll introduce you
to someone!
It seems like Lola's butt
is covered in ice.
She's all giddy. Who is that?
Hurry up.
- Wait, who is that?
- These guys are taking so long!
His name is...
Jin Ho!
You?
What are you doing here?
You know, I'm gonna stay here.
You can't stay here!
Why?
- Because...
- Who is that? Your ex?
- Him? My ex?
- Is he your ex?
What ex? That's impossible,
Lola!
What are you saying?
Why does it seem like there's
something?
Is there something?
Well, the three of us
are friends. Right?
We're friends, right?
Yeah.
Friends.
My God, you guys are driving me
crazy.
I was so nervous about you.
I thought I was going to have,
you know, a rival for my baby.
It's a good thing you said you
were friends.
Because then,
he'll sleep in your room.
What is this? It's annoying.
Okay, you take care of this,
okay?
Is he gonna show you the room,
I'll see you later, okay?
What's up, friend?
You called at the wrong time.
What are you doing here?
Your place is better!
Because you're still in danger
and Theresa is still out there.
I'm here to protect you,
to be your bodyguard.
For free?
Even if it's free,
I don't need a bodyguard!
I don't need you to protect me.
I know taekwondo.
Yeah, that's automatic.
But what if you're in trouble?
At least we have someone
to call. Right, oppa?
Are you talking to me?
Yeah.
That's what they call Korean
guys, right?
Oppa!
Yeah, but you know...
Okay, we can't do anything
if he wants to live here.
You can live here.
Just stay out of my way.
Clear?
Clear!
You know, you won't even notice
me because I'm good at my job.
Whatever.
Come.
I'll show you to our room, Oppa.
The Congressman's people are
still picking up our supplies.
They're on their way
to the factory.
They've doubled their orders
now.
I'll also make sure that their
route is clear
so that the police won't be
blocking them anymore.
Good.
Our operations have been smooth
again
since that Delgado was locked
up.
Maybe that policeman can
perform a miracle,
and we'll have another problem.
Why don't we just finish him
off?
Hey.
Just chill.
You, you're making your own
ghost.
Because I want to put a bullet
in that Delgado's head
so he can become a real ghost.
That's Parak's strategy.
I'm sure he's already cooking up
his plan.
He knows what to do, right?
Hello, Joey?
Godfather, can we meet?
It's important.
Sure. Why? What's that about?
It's about the evidence
I was talking about
that will help Father to be
free.
Joey?
Yes, Elai?
I just want to remind you
about our recording.
We've set up here.
Shocks. I'm sorry. I forgot.
I'm just here at Joey's house.
I just really have to talk
to her
because I think she's up
to something bad.
I'll be back. I promise.
Okay.
Bye.
Lord, I'm not that kind,
but why do my blessings seem to
be at their maximum right now?
Yes?
Is Joey there?
Is it possible to talk to her?
What's that?
Oh my, Joey is already gone,
she left already.
Why would you look for someone
who isn't there?
I mean, I'm here.
Will you please stop?
Didn't I tell you
I'm going by myself?
I told you I'm your bodyguard.
I'm here to protect you
from any possible attacker.
As for me, I'll watch over Oppa.
Please. I'm going alone.
Godfather...
- Godfather.
- My child.
How are you?
What evidence are you talking
about?
What's that about?
The day Ramon Orbos died,
I saw someone a woman and her
companions torturing him...
And then I took a video.
Here it is.
Did you ask your people
if they saw a flash drive?
It contains a video of me and
Ramon that I need to recover.
So this is it?
Yes, Godfather.
Please watch over my wife
and daughter.
Help me protect my family.
You shouldn't trust anyone.
Your father wants to warn you
because we don't know
who the real allies are.
Me, I'm thinking while you guys
are moving impulsively.
Focus on Berdugo's orders,
that is, to kill Delgado.
It's Diego...
Impossible.